(Penny:)Hey. So you guys ready
to order?
(Sheldon:)Since we come in
every Tuesday night at 6:00
(Sheldon:)and order the same exact thing,
and it's now 6:08,
(Sheldon:)I believe your question
not only answers itself
(Sheldon:)but also stands alongside
such other nonsensical queries
as "Who let the dogs out?"
and, uh, "How are they hanging""
(Penny:)Okay.
(Penny:)So, the usual, with extra spit
on Sheldon's hamburger.
(Amy:)Penny, a moment?
(Amy:)Do you have plans
this weekend?
(Penny:)Oh, gee, Amy, I'm sorry,
(Penny:)I'm actually pretty busy
this weekend.
(Sheldon:)Probably serving food
that was ordered today.
(Amy:)That's too bad. I was hoping
you could be my plus-one
(Amy:)at the Institute
of Interdisciplinary Studies'
(Amy:)symposium on the impact
of current scientific research
(Amy:)on societal interactions.
(Penny:)The what?
(Leonard:)It's an annual
science conference.
(Leonard:)We've all been invited to speak.
Oh! Oh, okay, well, you know,
like I said, I have plans, so...
(Amy:)Shame. Since you're
my best friend,
(Amy:)I thought it would be
a good bonding opportunity.